(Sheldon:)I wasn't
making a joke,
(Sheldon:)I was merely
stating fact.
(Sheldon:)Amy and I have a superior
relationship to yours.
(Leonard:)You don't honestly
think that, do you?
Y... Leonard,
(Sheldon:)I assumed you knew.
(Sheldon:)The ranking of
relationships in our circle
by quality is:
me and Amy,
(Scene:)Howard and Bernadette,
Raj and his girlfriend,
(Sheldon:)Penny and Chardonnay,
Penny and you.
LEONARD:
There isn't any ranking.
(Leonard:)And if there were, we wouldn't
be at the bottom of it.
(Penny:)Yeah, and actually,
I drink Sauvignon Blanc.
(Leonard:)That's the part
you have a problem with?
(Penny:)Relax.
AMY: There they go,
fighting again.
(Amy:)You'd never hear her talk
that way to Sauvignon Blanc.
(Raj:)So you never played
baseball as a kid,
(Raj:)not even
Little League?
(Howard:)Well, I was going to,
but the day of tryouts
(Howard:)I found my dad's
Playboy collection.